{
    "data": {
        "title": "JavaScript Flashcards",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "What are the three notes of a G major chord?",
                "hint": "Root third and fifth!",
                "answer": "G B D"
            },
            {
                "question": "What band wrote the song 'Scar Tissue'?",
                "hint": "The band name is also a spicy snack",
                "answer": "The Red Hot Chili Peppers"
            },
            {
                "question": "What note is a perfect 5th above C?",
                "hint": "Just count!",
                "answer": "G"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who were the two main composers of the classical period?",
                "answer": "Haydn and Mozart"
            },
            {
                "question": "What composer became more and more deaf as they got older?",
                "hint": "Think romantic period!",
                "answer": "Beethoven"
            },
            {
                "question": "What Miles Davis album started the modal jazz movement?",
                "hint": "The color of the sky",
                "answer": "Kind of Blue"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the 4 notes that create an Ab major7 chord?",
                "hint": "Root third fifth and major 7th",
                "answer": "Ab C Eb G"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the piano piece titled \"Clair de Lune\"?",
                "hint": "Initals are CD",
                "answer": "French composer Claude Debussy"
            },
            {
                "question": "What solo instrument does Gustav Mahler's 5th symphony start with?",
                "hint": "Brass!",
                "answer": "Trumpet"
            },
            {
                "question": "How many symphonies did Beethoven write?",
                "hint": "It's more then 5!",
                "answer": "9"
            },
            {
                "question": "What key is J.S Bach's 6th cello suite in?",
                "hint": "It's not a flat key",
                "answer": "D major"
            },
            {
                "question": "What musician was popular during the early jazz era and wrote the songs \"Jeepers Creepers\" and \"What a Wonderful World\"?",
                "hint": "Satchmo!",
                "answer": "Louis Armstrong"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the notes in the B mixolydian mode?",
                "hint": "Major scale with a flat 7th",
                "answer": "B C# D# E F# G# A"
            },
            {
                "question": "What style of jazz was Charlie Parker a master at?",
                "hint": "It starts with a \"B\"",
                "answer": "Bebop"
            },
            {
                "question": "What would a I V Vi IV progression be in the key of F major?",
                "hint": "The second chord is C major",
                "answer": "F major, C major, d minor, Bb Major"
            }
        ]
    }
}